Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.eleven Mss.B.B61.inventory11
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents R
  - Reimer, Otto E. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 25
  - Reinhard, J.R. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 29; 2p
  - Reinhardt, Aurelia (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 27
  - Reinhardt, G.P. (Box 74)
    - To Boas and enc., 1933 Sep. 12
      - Staebel, Nazi propag., 1933 Sep. 11
    - To Boas and enc., 1934 June 18
    - To Boas and enc., 1934 Jan. 16
    - To Boas and enc., 1940 Apr. 25
  - Reinhardt, Max (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 May 20; 3p
  - Reinhardt, Walter, German Consul. General (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 3
      - enc. from Walter, Max & Stelz, Ludwig, 1922 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 22; 2p
  - Reinhold, Heinrich (Box 74)
    - From Boas re: Emerg. Soc., Aid Europ. Sci. and Art, 1920 Aug. 16; 2p
  - Reisinger, Hugo (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 28
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 30
  - Reiss, Lionel S. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 29
  - Reiss, W. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1885 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1885 July 2
    - To Boas, 1885 Aug. 14; 2p
  - Reissig, Herman F. (Box 74)
    - 1938 May 19
    - From Boas, 1938 May 23
    - From Boas, 1938 May 23
    - From Boas, 1938 June 7
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 24; 2p
      - see McConnell, F.J., 1939 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 27
  - Reko, V.A. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 15
  - Remick, E.W. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 17
  - Remsen, Ira (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 13
  - Remy, Alfred (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 18
  - Remy, Arthur S.J. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 21
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 21
    - From Boas, 1925 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 9
  - Renaud, E.B. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1924 June 5; 3p
  - Réndon, V.A. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1917 June 13
  - Rendueles, Roberto (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 18
    - To Jacobs, Paula, 1938 Feb. 2
  - Renger, A. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 20
  - Renner, G.T. (Box 74)
    - To Berkey, and enc. on primitive religion, 1927 Mar. 21
  - Renner, O. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1925 Arp. 27a
  - Research in American Indian Languages (Box 74)
    - Minutes, 1st meet., Exec. Committee, 1927 June 12; 2p
  - Rest (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 18; 4p
  - Retail Dry Goods Ass'n (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1931 June 10
  - Retius, Gustaf, 1908 Jan. 10; 2p (Box 74)
    - 1910 May 3, 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 27
  - Rettmann, James (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 21
  - Retzius, G. -- [see Retsius] (Box 74)
  - Reuter, J.B. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 13
    - To Boas with enc. from Deloria, E.C., 1939 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas with enc. from Deloria, E.C., 1939 Apr. 4
  - Reuterskiold, C.A. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1924 Sep. 2
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1924 Sep. 5
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 3
  - Revel, Bernard (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 12
  - Revere, Tony (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 30; 2p
  - Réville, A. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 20; 4p
  - Revista do Arquivo, Editors (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 28
  - Reymert, Martin L. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 28
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 28
  - Reynold, G. de (Box 74)
    - See League of Nations, 1922 Nov. 4
  - Reynolds, Agnes (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 14
  - Reynolds, Rollo G. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 4
    - To Boas - see FB Open letter, Spain, Replies, 1938 Jan.
  - Reznikoff, Ida
    - See Spencer, Louise C., 1940 Feb. 24
  - Rhiett [?], Benedict
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 7; 4p
  - Rhoades, Charles J. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1930 June 24
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 1
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 29
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 31
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1930 June 25
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1931 June 6
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1932 May 21
    - To Hertz, R., 1930 May 17
  - Rhoades, Lewis A. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 11; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 21; 2p
  - Rhympis [?], B. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 28
  - Riappo, A. (Box 75)
    - See Mikhaylitchenko, 1941 Jan. 15
  - Ribero, E.F. [E.Z.?] (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 19
  - Ricciardi, Fernando L. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 29
  - Rice, F.W. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1924 Apr. 8
  - Rice, John L. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 17
      - same to Dublin, L., 1941 July 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 5
  - Rice, P. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1926 May 26; 4p
    - From Boas, 1926 Sep. 24
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 27
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 29
  - Rice, Paul North (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 25
  - Rice, Stuart A. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1928 May 24; 3p
  - Rice, Wm. G. [?] Jr. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 11
  - Rich (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 9; 2p
  - Richard, Ernst (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1908 May 1
    - From Boas, 1908 May 11
    - From Boas, 1910 June 7
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 July 6
    - To Boas, 1905 July 12
    - To Boas, 1905 July 26
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1906 May 4
    - To Boas, 1910 July 8
  - Richardson, D.S. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 5
  - Richardson, Ethel (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 4
    - From Boas, 1927 June 8
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 1
  - Richardson, W.S. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 26
  - Richardson-Wilson, I. (Box 75)
    See Wright, Corrine
    - co-signer, 1934 Feb. 2
  - Richarz, Franz (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1886 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1886 Aug. 6 and 1898 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1898 Sep. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 31; 3p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 4; card
  - Richter (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1930 May 17
  - Richter, Mrs. Fernanda (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1
      - see Germania, Pres., 1905 Nov. 1
  - Richter, Henry (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 20
  - Richter, R. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 21
  - Richthofen, Fr. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 28
  - Rickardown, D.S. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 1
  - Ricketts, P.C. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1918 June 12
  - Ridder, Hermann -- (N.Y. Staats-Zeitung) (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 31; ?
    - From Hexamer, C.J., 1914 June 2
  - Ridder, Victor F. -- (N.Y. Staats-Zeitung & Staats-Herold) (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 24
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 5
  - Rideout, H.M. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 1; 2p
    - To Smith, H.J., 1910 Aug. 1; 2p
    - From Smith, H.J., 1910 Aug. 9
  - Ridgely (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 18
  - Rieber, C.H. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 16
  - Riesberg, F.W. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 29
    - To New Era Ptg. Co., 1918 Apr. 11
  - Riesen, E.R. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1931 May 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1931 May 7
    - To Kidder, A.V., 1931 Apr. 21
    - From Kidder, A.V., 1931 Apr. 27
  - Riess, Bernard F. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1939 July 18
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 9
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, E.P., 1942 Dec. 29
  - Riess, Ernst (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 31
      see also Kiess, E.
  - Riggs, Thomas L. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1937 May 24
    - From Boas, 1937 July 15
  - Rijichart (Box 75)
    - See Boas to Engerrand, G.C., 1913 Oct. 31
  - Riohter (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1921 May 11
  - Rink, Hinrich J. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1884 Dec. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1885 Feb.?
    - To Boas, 1885 June 5
    - To Boas, 1885 July 7
    - To Boas, 1885 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1885 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1885 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1885 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1885 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1886 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1886 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1886 July 21
    - To Boas, 1886 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1887 Aug. 14
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1889 May 29
  - Rink, Signe (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1903 Sep. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 19
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1904 Sep. 7; 4p
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 23; 4p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 10; 3p
  - Rinner, Dr. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1937 July 7
  - Rintelen (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1932 June 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 30
  - Rios, F. de los (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1937 July 8
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 2
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 13
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 16
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 23
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 13
      - open letter re: Catholic Church in Spain, 1937 Sep. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 18
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 28
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 12
    - To Efron, D., 1937 Mar. 23
  - Ripley (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 17
  - Ripley, Wm. Z. (M.I.T.) (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1896 July 23
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 11
  - Rippe, Fritz (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 31
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 4
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 17
    - From Boas, 1933 July 24
    - To Boas, 1924 Sep. 5
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 13; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 18
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 31; 2p
  - Riste, V. (Box 75)
    - enc. with Sapir, 1931 Jan. 15; 3p
  - Ritchie (Box 75)
  - Ritchie, Frank (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 7
    - From Ritchie, 1936 Dec. 2; 2p
  - Ritchie, W.A. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1930 Aug. 11
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 9; 2p
  - Ritt, Estelle (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 6
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 22; 3p
  - Rittein, R.T. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1915 May 10
  - Rittenberg, Louis (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 27
  - Ritter, L.A. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 22
  - Rittig, J. (Box 75)
    - [To Dr. A. Jacobi?], 1884 Oct. 11
  - Ritting, F.V. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1923 June 19
  - Rivarola, Rodolfo (Box 75)
    - To Boas re Debenetti, 1917 Aug. 31
  - Rivaud (Box 75)
    - See Bouglé, C., 1931 Mar. 15
      - co-signers; Fauconnet, P.
      - Gilson, E.
      - Blondel, Ch.
      - Rivet
      - Mauss, M.
  - River, G.L. (Box 75)
    - To Cattell, J.M.K., 1913 May 21
  - Rivers, W.H.R. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 12; 2p
      - (enc. Malnutrition, 1922 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 June 11
  - Rivet, Paul (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 11
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 23; 3p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 3 and Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1920 May 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 13
    - From Boas, 1920 May 28
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1924 Sep. 4
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1925 July 13
    - From Boas, 1925 Aug. 8
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 18
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 30
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 17
    - From Boas, 1933 June 26
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 8
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 18; 4p
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 18; 3p
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 13
    - From Boas, 1937 May 27
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1941 Aug. 25
    - To Boas, 1909 June 8
    - To Boas, 1919 July 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 4; 6p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 14; 5p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 June 7; 4p
      - enc. typed list, 1920 June 22; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 29
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 17; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 18; 3p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 13; 4p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 12
    - To Boas, 1924 May 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 16
    - To Boas, 1924 Sep. 7; 4p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 17; 4p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 26; 3p
    - To Boas, 1925 June 26
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 23; 8p
    - To Boas, 1925 Oct. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 19; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 1; 4p
      - see Bouglé, C., 1931 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1931 July 15; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 27
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 27; 13p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 13
    - To Boas, 1933 June 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 16
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 16
      - see Rabkine, Louis vita, 1940 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 14; 8p
    - To WL??, 1920 Dec. 31
  - Riviore, G.H. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 11
  - Rizer, Chief Clerk, Bureau, Ethnology (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1893 Jan. 28; 2p
  - Rizer, H.C. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1909 May 5
  - Robbins, Miss (Box 75)
    - From Andrews, H.A., 1923 July 24
  - Robbins, Jane E. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 28
    - From Boas, 1908 June 5
    - From Boas, 1908 June 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1908 May 29
    - To Boas, 1908 June 3
  - Robbins, Jeannette C., Secretary to Gifford (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1927 July 19
    - To Boas, 1927 July 24
  - Robbins, W.J. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 17
  - Robeles, Cecilo A. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1912 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1912 May 3
    - From Boas, 1912 Sep. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 May 24
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 14
    - To Boas, 1913 July 7
  - Roberts (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 24
  - Roberts, H.H. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 19
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 21
    - From Boas, 1920 May 25
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 25
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1925 May 12
    - From Boas, 1925 May 14
    - From Boas, 1925 May 19
    - From Boas, 1925 May 26
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 28; 4p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 June 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 10; 4p
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 28; 6p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 23; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 1; 2p
    - Recommendation, see FB, 1923 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 13
    - To Boas, 1925 May 18
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 2; 2p
    - From Beckwith, M.W., 1921 May 15; 2p
      - originally M.W. to FB
    - From Mason, J.A., 1920 Nov. 7
  - Roberts, R.B. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 18
  - Roberts, Sylvia S. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1939 May 3
  - Robertson, D.A., Secretary to President, University of Chicago (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1920 July 16
  - Robins, Henry B. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 5
  - Robinson (Box 75)
    - From Boas - see FB to Giddings, F.H., 1913 Jan. 18
  - Robinson, Anna E. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1937 May 14
  - Robinson, B.L. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 6
  - Robinson, Edward (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 17
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 15
    - To Butler, Nicholas M., 1912 Jan. 25; 2p
  - Robinson, F.B. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 3
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1934 May 5
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 22
  - Robinson, F.W. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 3
  - Robinson, J.H., 1913 Oct. 28 (Box 75)
    - 1917 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 24
    - From Boas, 1926 May 18
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1926 May 18
    - To Boas, 1925 June 12; 2p
  - Robinson, W.P. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 8
  - Robison, Jesse (Box 75)
    - enc.:, 1938 Apr. 4
      - Allen, Jay open letter, Mar. 25
  - Roche, Josephine (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 3
  - Roche [?], V. [?] (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 1
  - Rock, E.J. (Box 75)
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 9
  - Rock, Nathan L. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 21
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 75)
    - Appropriation '33-'34, 1934 Dec. 31
    - See Anon. to Gulkowitsch, L., Dir., European office, soc. sciences, 1935 Dec. 30
      See Vincent, George E.
  - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (Box 75)
    See Loeb, Jacques
    Uhlenhuth, E.
  - Rockefeller, N.A. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 14
  - Rockhill, W.W. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 21
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Mar. 23
  - Rockwell, W.W. (Box 75)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1931 May 9
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 12
  - Rodakiewicz, E.
    - From Boas, 1917 May 22
    - To Boas, 1917 May 21
    - To Boas, 1917 June 26
    - To Nat'l Inst. Soc. Sciences, Members, 1917 May 11; 2p
  - Rodeman, Georg (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 12
  - Rodenberg, C. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1906 June 29; 2p
  - Rodenbough, T.F. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 28
  - Rodenfeld, K. (Box 76)
    - See Boas open letter, 1935 Dec. 31
  - Rodenwaldt, Gerhard (Box 76)
    - To Boas, mimeo letter, 1922 Dec. 5; 3p
  - Rodlof (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1903 Sep. 28
  - Rodman, S.J. (Box 76)
    - See Dearborn, N.H., 1938 Sep. 24
      - Co-signers; Morris, N.
      - Kern, P.J.
      - Dearborn, N.H.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 21
    - From Jackson, Gardner, 1939 Mar. 4
  - Rodriguez, F.M. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1911 Dec. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 26
  - Roeck, Fritz (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 29; 2p
  - Roele, J. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 18
  - Roepe, J. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 10
  - Roeter, Ralph (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 22
    - To Boas with D. Brewster, 1939 May 10
  - Rogers, C. Gilbert (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1906 Sep. 18
  - Rogers, F.K. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 16
  - Rogers, Pauline (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 31
  - Rogers, S.L. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 6
  - Rohde, Hanna (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 3
  - Rohmkopf, E. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 29; 2p
  - Rohrbach, Hans (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 29; 4p
  - Rohrbach, Paul (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 2
    - re: Deutsche Akademie, 1929 Dec. 31; 2p
  - Rojas (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1911 July 7
  - Roland-Marcel, P. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 18
  - Rolland, Fred (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 25
  - Roller, Romain (Box 76)
    - See Catt, C.C., 1937 Feb. 10
  - Rollins [?], E.W.B. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 2
  - Rollins, H.E. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 14
  - Rolutschek, Robert (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1942 Sep. 14
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1942 July 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1942 Aug. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1942 Sep. 10; 8p
    - To Boas, 1942 Sep. 14
    - To Boas, 1942 Sep. 23